{
  "LevelId": 4,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 30,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "MEMBERS",
      "question": "People in a group"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "SUNRISE",
      "question": "Morning's first light"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "ENVELOP",
      "question": "Paper container for letters"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "FINANCE",
      "question": "Money management"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "DESKTOP",
      "question": "Computer surface"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "TRAFFIC",
      "question": "Congested road situation"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "COMPANY",
      "question": "The Business organization is a"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "GLASSES",
      "question": "you wear to improve vision or protect your eyes"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "CAPITAL",
      "question": "The primary city where a country's government is located"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "BREAKFAST",
      "question": "Morning meal"
    }
  ]
}